

LUKAS JURGILAS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

GET IN TOUCH

- Mobile: +37064507633
- jurgilasslukas@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/lukas-jurgilas
- 🚅 lukasjcode.github.io/React-Portfolio

PERSONAL SKILLS

- -Time management
- -Fast learner
- -Practical
- -Team worker
- -Motivated

LANGUAGES

- -Lithuanian (Native)
- -English (Fluent)
- -Danish (Intermediate)

SKILLS

- -C# .NET, Node.js
- -Java, Javascript
- -HTML, CSS, React
- -SQL, MongoDB
- -Unity
- -SCRUM
- -UML

HOBBIES



ABOUT ME

I am 25 years – old, motivated, passionate, creative, communicative recent graduated software engineer. Always taking my tasks seriously with a motivation to do it as fast and as good as I can. Comfortable at analyzing problems and providing simple and effective solutions. A friendly, possessing urge to succeed and develop new skills in my field of interest. Currently residing in Denmark. Willing to relocate.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- MITA-TEKNIK A/S, RØDKÆRSBRO

Software Engineer (2020.03 - 2022.01)

-Worked on C# based Unity mobile application. Utilizing various aspects of C# language and integrating API calls. The application was released to both Google Play and Apple App Store.

- EON REALITY DENMARK, VIBORG

Software Engineering intern (2019.08 - 2020.01)

-Worked with cutting edge technologies such as VR/AR/MR. Produced many smaller projects using Unity and C# language. Interacted with various clients and showcased projects to the public.

- VIA UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, DENMARK

Student employee in Makerspace Viborg (2019.11 - 2020.01)

- RANDERS CITY CAMP, RANDERS, DENMARK Cleaning assistant (2019.07 2019.08)
- ÅRSTIDERNE A/S, BARRIT, DENMARK Bag machine operator in a warehouse (2018.02 - 2019.01)

EDUCATION

-VIA UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, DENMARK

Aug 2017 - Jan 2021

Bachelors degree in Software Engineering

-KLAIPĖDOS "ĄŽUOLYNO" GYMNASIUM, LITHUANIA

2014-2017 High school diploma